

ABOUT ME

I graduated from UIN Syarif Hidayatullah Jakarta majoring in Physics with a focus on Instrumentation Physics. Experience in analyzing experimental data has leverage my skills in identifying problems and troubleshooting capabilities. I have an understanding of hardware (computer and robot hardware) and software (Arduino, Python) based on my experience in disassembling and designing hardware and also creating program algorithms.

CONTACT

Address : Jl. Kyai Maja RT 03/RW 03, Kel. Panunggangan,

Kec. Pinang, Kota Tangerang 15143

Phone Number : 081906795257

Email : mcgalihramdhan@gmail.com Linkedin : linkedin.com/in/mcgalih/

EDUCATION

Universitas Islam Negeri Syarif Hidayatullah Jakarta

May 2017 - January 2023

Bachelor of Science in Physics, GPA: 3.52/4.0

COURSES

RevoU (online course)

RevoU Mini Course Digital Marketing

RevoU (online course)

RevoU Fundamental Course Software Engineering

RevoU (online course)

RevoU Mini Course Data Analytics

SKILLS

Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PPT)
Object oriented programming (Arduino, Python)
Web design (HTML, CSS, Javascript)
Graphic design (Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator)

EXPERIENCES

Administrator Staff | 06/2023 - 10/2023

PT. Lutfi Rizki Abadi

- Checking employee attendance through their fingerprints and absence permits
- Calculating employee overtime hours
- Organize employee databases and the duration of their work contracts
- · Monitor the daily activities of the client's company

Laboratory Assistant | 02/2021 - 12/2021

Pusat Laboratorium Terpadu UIN Syarif Hidayatullah Jakarta

- Checking and calibrating the tools before doing experiments
- Teach students how to operate and achieve results according to the practicum module.
- Correcting and assessing student experimental reports

Graphic Designer | 08/2018 – 01/2019

Ekspedisi 2018 event, HIMAFI UIN Syarif Hidayatullah Jakarta

- Create an instagram posts
- Create a nametag design
- Create a banner design

PROJECTS

Automatic Moving Charity Box

Github link: github.com/mcgalih/Charity-Box-Car

- Designed a storage box device that can move automatically and following the track line
- Control the device movement by placing a hand in front or behind of the device

Card Security System Charity Box

Github link: github.com/mcgalih/Charity-Box-Card

- Designed a storage box device that can only be opened by certain card(s)
- Can register a new card(s) as a key

Nomor Ijazah Nasional SK BAN-PT APT [Nilai] SK BAN-PT PRODI [Nilai] 452012023000168

: No. 25/SK/BAN-PT/Akred/PT/II/2018 [A] : No. 6929/SK/BAN-PT/Ak-PPJ/S/XI/2020 [B]



KEMENTERIAN AGAMA REPUBLIK INDONESIA UNIVERSITAS ISLAM NEGERI SYARIF HIDAYATULLAH JAKARTA



Memberikan Kepada:

Mochamad Galih Ramdhani

Lahir pada tanggal 12 Januari 1999 di Tangerang

I J A Z A H SARJANA SAINS (S.Si.)

FAKULTAS : Sains dan Teknologi

PROGRAM STUDI : Fisika

NOMOR INDUK MAHASISWA : 11170970000002

NOMOR INDUK KEPENDUDUKAN / PASPOR : 3671111201990001

TANGGAL LULUS : 27 Januari 2023

Dengan segala hak dan kewajiban yang berhubungan dengan gelar akademik ini.

Rektor

Prof. Dr. Hj. Amany Lubis, M.A.



Jakarta, 24 Februari 2023

Dekan

Ir. Nashrul Haklem, S.Sl., M.T., Ph.D NIP.19710608 200501 1 005.4



Universitas Islam Negeri SYARIF HIDAYATULLAH JAKARTA

TRANSKRIP AKADEMIK

Nomor Ijazah Nasional + 452012023000168

SK BAN-PT APT [N lai] : No. 25/SK/BAN-PT/Akred/PT/II/2018 [A]

Nama Tempat/Tgl.Lahir

Fakultas

MOCHAMAD GALIH RAMDHANI

: Tangerang, 12 Januari 1999

: Sains dan Teknologi

Program Studi : Fisika

Tanggal Lulus : 27 Januari 2023 NIM

IPK

Jenjang

Jumlah Kredit

: 11170970000002

: 31

: 161 SKS

3,52

Predikat Kelulusan Sangat Memuaskan Nomor Transkrip

Judul Skripsi

: B.F.9.ER 073692.2023

Rancang Bangun Kotak Amal Berjalan Otomatis Dengan Fungsi Deteksi Gelap-Terang Lantal.

Kode	Matakuliah	SKS	Nilai	Kode	Matakuliah	SKS	Nilai	Kode Matakuliah	SKS Nilai	Kode	Matakuliah	SKS Nila
BHS 6003	BAHASA ARAB	3	A	FIS 4078	PEMROGRAMAN SISTEM INSTRUMENTASI	3	Α					
BHS 6001	BAHASA INDONESIA	3	A	ris 5082	PENDAHULJAN FISIKA INTI	4	A					
BHS 6002	BAHASA INGGRIS	3	В	POL 2002	PENDIDIKAN KEWARGANEGARAAN	2	5					
BIO 2019	BICLOGI JMUN	2	В	FIS 5072	PENGOLAHAN SINYAL DIGITAL	2	4					
FIS 6069	DASAR-DASAR TELEKOMUNIKASI	3	A	FIS 4010	PRAKTEK BENGKEL	2	4					
FIS 4017	EKSPERIMEN FISIKA 1	2	В	AEI 6027	PRAKTEK KERLA LAPANGAN	3	Д					
FIS 6017	EKSFERIMEN FISIKA 2	2	В	FIS 4031	PRAKTIKUM FLEKTRONIKA	1	В					
FIS 5142	ELEKTORNIKA LANJUT	2	В	FIS 6139	PRAKTIKUM ELEKTRONIKA I ANJUT	1	A					
FIS 4033	ELEKTRONIKA	3	В	FIE 3013	PRAKTIKUM FISIKA DASAR 1	1 3	Α					
FIS 3003	FISIKA DASAR 1	3	A	FIS 4014	PRAKTIKUM FISIKA DASAR 2	1	٨					
FIS 4003	FISIKA DASAR 2	3	в	FIS 4092	PRAKTIKUM FISIKA KOMPUTASI	1	В					
FIS 4015	FISIKA KOMPUTAS	3	В	SAR 2002	PRAKTIKUM IBADAH	1	A					
FIS 6004	FISIKA KUANTUM	4	A	KIM 3047	PRAKTIKUM KIMIA DASAR	1	C		-			
FIS 5005	FISIKA MATEMATIKA 2	4	В	FIS 6029	PRAKT KUM MICROPROSESOR	1	A	Company of the Compan				
FIS 4005	FISIKA MATEMATIKA I	4	В	FIS 5081	PRAKT KUM PENGOLAHAN SINYAL DIGITAL	1	А	Rise and the second				
FIS 5007	FISIKA MODERN	3	А	SAR 2001	PRAKTIK JM QIROAH	1	В					
TIS 6018	FISIKA STATISTIK	1	В	FIS 3089	PRAKT KUM SISTEM DIGI <mark>T</mark> AL	1	Α			5)		
FIS 5020	FISIKA ZAT PADAT	4	Α	TIS 3088	PRAKTIKUM SISTEM KENDALI.	1	A	100000				
SEI 2237	GELOMBANG	3	В	FIS 5074	ROBOTIK	3	Α					
FIS 4002	ILMU PEDAGOGIK	2	В	JIN 4265	SEMINAR SKRIPSI	1	Α					
FIS 5071	INSTRUMENTASI FISIKA MEDIS	3	В	F185070	SISTEM DIGITAL	2	Α					
SAG 2002	ISLAM DAN ILMU PENGETAHUAN	3	Α	FIS 6074	SISTEM KENDAL	2	А					
MAT 3018	KALKULUS 1	.2	A	FIS 6065	SISTEM SENSOR	3	В	A STATE OF THE PERSON NAMED IN COLUMN TWO IS NOT THE PERSON NAMED IN COLUMN TWO IS		Yes		
MAT 4018	KALKULUS 2	3	В	STA3023	STATISTIKA	3	В	and the second s				
ABI 2019	KEW RAUSA IAAN	2	В	SAC 6001	STJDUSLAM	4	А			Jakar.a, 24 Februari	2023	
KIM 3015	EIMIA DASAR	2	В	FIS 6072	TEORI RANGKAIAN	5	Д		/	Dekan		
ABI 5013	KULIAH KERJA NYATA (KKN)	3	A	FIS 5014	THERMODINAMIKA	5	Α		1/3	COX. W		
FIS 3083	MEDAN ELEKTROMAGNET 1	4	ь	ABI 9014	SKRIPSI	6	A		1/2/			
FIS 7085	MEDAN ELKTROMAGNET 2	3	В						(*	un	.Si., M.T., P1.D	
FIS 5021	MEKANIKA	2	В						اماا	NIP 19: 10608 20050		
FIS 6021	MEKANIKA KI ASIKA	A	A						113	NA R 1 19 10608 20050	1.1(05*	
MA" 4036	METODE NUMERIK	2	Α							OUR INDO		
ABI 3021	METODOLOGI PENELITIAN FISIKA	3	A									
FIS 506?	MICROPROSESOR	3	C									
POL 2001	PANCASILA	2	Α							- Control and Application and		



PT. LUTFI RIZKI ABADI

Ruko Centra Niaga E Blok T18/12 Citra Raya, Mekar Bakti – Panongan, Tamgerang 15710

Telp: 082210536829

Email: lutfirizkiabadi@gmail.com

CERTIFICATE OF EMPLOYMENT

SURAT KETERANGAN BEKERJA

No:087/HR&GA/SKB-LIRA/X/2023

This is to certify that

Dengan ini menerangkan bahwa

Name Nama

: MOCHAMAD GALIH RAMDHANI

Employee's ID number

: 2200660067

NIK .Karyawan

. ____,

Division/Dept
Divisi/Dept

: STAFF ADMINISTRASI

Position

: KOORDINATOR LAPANGAN

<u>Jabatan</u>

Year of service(s)

Masa Kerja

: 26 JUNI 2023 S/D 25 OKTOBER 2023

Reason for leaving

: RESIGN

Alasanberhenti

We would like express our deepest thanks to Mr. Mochamad Galih Ramdhani who worked well and satisfactorily during him working period at the company

Kami mengucapkan terimakasih banyak kepada Sdr. Mochamad Galih Ramdhani yang telah bekerja dengan baik dan penuh tanggung jawab pada perusahaan ini.

Dikeluarkandi: Tangerang

PadaTanggal: 25 Oktober 2023

PT. LUTFI RIZKI ABADI

